{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "Children,_______ in the house. You make too much noise!",
      "a": "you don't play",
      "b": "don't you play",
      "c": "play not",
      "d": "don't play",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Come on Sandra, _______ about it.",
      "a": "let's talk",
      "b": "let we",
      "c": "talk us",
      "d": "let's we",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Please, Jimmy,_______ on the radio yet!",
      "a": "you don't switch",
      "b": "don't switch",
      "c": "switch not",
      "d": "not switch",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Boys,_______ play with you!",
      "a": "let I",
      "b": "let me",
      "c": "you let me",
      "d": "let me you",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me... \n+ Let somebody (us, me, her, them",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Mum, I am going to do it again _______ see you do it!",
      "a": "Don't let me",
      "b": "Don't let I",
      "c": "I don't let me",
      "d": "I don't",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Bob,______ the children to stop making that noise!",
      "a": "let",
      "b": "tell",
      "c": "say",
      "d": "let you",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me... ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Tom, _______ that, will you!",
      "a": "you stop doing",
      "b": "stop you doing",
      "c": "stop to do",
      "d": "stop doing",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me... \n- Stop Verb-ing: not continue doing something",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Please, _______ to see me.",
      "a": "let the boys come",
      "b": "come the boys",
      "c": "let come the boys",
      "d": "let's the boys come",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me... \n- Let somebody do something",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Sheila,_______ go to the cinema tonight!",
      "a": "let we",
      "b": "let us",
      "c": "we let",
      "d": "we let's",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me... \n- Let do something",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The children will do it. OK,______ do it!",
      "a": "tell them",
      "b": "let them",
      "c": "-",
      "d": "let they",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me...",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    }
  ]
}